To
celebrate the 10th anniversary of the establishment of the
Prudential Ky Anh General Agency Office, the
Prudential Ky Anh General Agency Office, in coordination with the
Ky Anh Town Red Cross Society, organized the "
Together with You to School" program, which included activities to fulfill children's dreams.
Leaders of the Ky Anh Town Labor Union, the
Red Cross Society,
local authorities, and agents were
present at the ceremony. During the event, the
Prudential Ky Anh General Agency Office
presented 10 gifts worth nearly 15 million
VND to disadvantaged students
in the ward. These meaningful gifts serve as
encouragement and motivation for the
children to excel in their studies. This is an
annual activity. On the occasion of the anniversary of the
establishment of the Ky Anh General Agency Office and the
continuous efforts and
development of production and business activities, creating
jobs for hundreds of
local workers over the years, the
Prudential Ky Anh General Agency Office has always
supported the
Ky Anh Town Red Cross Society in humanitarian and charitable activities such as providing
bicycles, scholarships, and educational support.
Students and young people giving Tet gifts to
the poor will
continue to implement and expand these activities in
the future to support
people in difficult circumstances in the
area. At the ceremony, delegates and customers
were advised on the basic benefits of
participating in Prudential life insurance.
This is the first life insurance company to be present
in Vietnam in
1999. Since its establishment,
this company has donated 26,000 billion VND to
social welfare activities and is also the
first foreign life insurance company to be
awarded the
Labor Medal of what class by the Party and State in 2014?